[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
"The Missing Piece"
(Episode 5)
My big brother's birthday is coming up.
Shen.
What are you planning to
get my brother for his birthday?
Help me figure it out.
I'm trying to think of something too.
A regular gift would be so boring.
Why don't you buy two plane tickets?
How about taking a trip abroad together?
Even the best gift can't
compare to a beautiful memory.
Don't you think?
A trip?
Yeah.
That island I went to with Zhou
Yang last time was pretty nice.
Blue skies, white clouds, the beach.
Just thinking about it feels romantic.
Shen.
What do you think of my idea?
What if Mr. Ji and I vacationed on the
island where Zhou Yang proposed to Ji An'an?
Wouldn't that be a little awkward?
It's actually a pretty good idea.
But the holidays are coming up.
There'll definitely be a lot
going on at the company
Mr. Ji may not have time.
Come on.
Just wait until he gets back and
ask him directly.
A perfect couple like you two
on an island.
Just imagining it sounds wonderful.
You should focus on what
you're going to get him.
Come on.
This is driving me crazy.
Big brother, come on.
Time to eat.
Yeah.
Big brother.
Are you busy in early
February? Are you free?
Why are you suddenly asking?
What's up? Is something wrong?
Come on.
Just tell me if you're free.
Just tell me whether you're busy.
If you're not busy,
Shen wants to go with you.
An'an.
I need to check my schedule for next month.
Eat first.
This is good.
Try this.
Have a taste.
I'm full.
Go give my brother a little push.
Otherwise, he'll forget about it again
I still have to do the dishes.
Come on. That's not important.
Go, go.
Okay, okay, okay.
Go
I'm going.
That's right.
Those few days in early February.
I don't care how you do it.
Move things up or push them back.
Just make sure you're
free in early February.
I never would've guessed.
Mr. Ji can be pretty cute sometimes.
Go ahead.
What exactly are you and An'an planning?
Early February is my birthday.
An'an suggested
that you and I go on vacation
to the island she went to before.
And you agreed?
As long as Mr. Ji is okay with it.
I have no objection.
I don't like that island.
Let's pick somewhere else.
I'm free those days.
I'll have my secretary book the tickets.
Just pack your bags over the next few days.
I never would've guessed
Mr. Ji was such a good liar too.
Mr. Ji.
Do you actually like me a little bit?
If I didn't like you,
why would I get turned on by you?
What's wrong?
Are you busy today, Mr. Ji?
I made a last-minute appointment
with the owner of that media company.
I'd like to discuss a partnership
with you while you're available today.
Does it have to be today?
I need to take care of An'an's
wedding arrangements this afternoon.
Today would be best.
The company's chairman is
leaving on a business trip soon.
Why don't you have
Mr. Shen accompany An'an first?
It won't take up much of your time.
Oh.
What's wrong?
Zhao Yi.
He arranged a meeting for me
with the owner of an AI company later.
I contacted him before
to ask him to make the connection.
Oh.
As for An'an this afternoon...
Go in my place for now.
I'll head over as soon as I can.
Mm.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
It's okay.
Shen.
Thank goodness you were here today.
Without you
with my brother acting like that
I might've had to come alone today.
It's okay.
It's the least I could do.
Help me take a look.
Do you think this one looks better
or this one?
I think they're both nice.
They're just different styles.
Yeah.
Whichever one you like.
I'm so nervous.
Do you think I should wear
a satin wedding dress
or one made of tulle?
Oh.
What if there are a lot of people that day...?
[Mrs. Zhou]
Auntie, I have to tell you
I've really been wanting
to see you since I came back.
Isn't that Mrs. Zhou and Zhou Chu?
Let's go say hi.
I'm not going.
It's okay.
Come on.
Don't be nervous.
We'll be family from now on.
I'm not close with Mrs. Zhou.
You go.
Then I'll go by myself.
Yeah.
Take a break first.
I hope
you understand your place.
Auntie
I didn't...!
Auntie Zhou.
Oh.
An'an.
What are you doing here?
You look beautiful today.
Let's talk over there.
Yeah.
Okay.
If he were here,
no one would dare humiliate me like this.
[Ji An'an: Shen, I'm not feeling well,
I'm resting in room 2505, come up ASAP]
Mr. Ji once told me
that An'an has been frail
and sickly since she was little.
If she feels even the slightest discomfort
she has to go to the hospital right away.
Hello.
The number you have dialed
is temporarily unavailable.
An'an is clearly with Mrs. Zhou.
Why wouldn't she call someone
from the Zhou family if she felt sick?
Even if she sees me as family
and feels reassured only when she sees me,
she could've just called.
Why send me a text?
What's wrong?
Mr. Ji.
An'an said she wasn't feeling well.
She's in room 2505 at the Dynasty Hotel.
But I can't get in touch with her.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
An'an is with the Zhou family.
It should be nothing serious.
Be careful.
If anything seems wrong
call an ambulance immediately.
Okay.
An'an.
Why did it take you so
long to get the clothes?
Shen Mo.
What are you doing here?
Where's An'an?
She told me she wasn't feeling well.
Open it.
Can't you open it?
We...
We were set up.
That bastard Zhou Chu.
Your brother did this.
He spilled coffee on me.
Then he booked this room
so I could change clothes.
What about you?
Why are you here?
He took Miss Ji's phone
and told me she wasn't feeling well
and asked me to come check on her.
But this is way too coincidental.
You and An'an are both at this hotel.
Miss Ji loves the afternoon tea here.
We come here all the
time to have it together.
Zhou Chu suggested that today...
we should come to this hotel
for afternoon tea as a family.
Looks like your wonderful little brother
has done his homework.
He even knows where Miss Ji and I go.
No wonder I thought something was off
when I saw him at the auto show that day.
I suspect
he already knows about
our past relationship.
So what if he does?
Is there anyone in your
family who doesn't know?
Besides...
you and I have nothing to
do with each other anymore.
Hello. Front desk?
The door to Room 2505 is locked.
Could you come up and unlock it?
Thanks.
Hello.
Mr. Ji.
What the hell are you doing?
Mr. Ji, Mr. Ji.
Do you think Ji Mingxuan is a good person?
He's just like Zhou Chu.
They'll do anything to get what they want.
What are you trying to say?
What am I trying to say?
I've already looked into everything.
Yes.
It was my fault.
I went abroad with An'an behind your back.
But guess what Ji Mingxuan did.
He told my parents about your
identity and our relationship.
And you still treated him like your savior.
He was the one who started all this.
Stay away from Zhou Yang.
Do you understand?
The day I was kidnapped
[Zhou Yang]
I called the police first.
Then I called Zhou Yang.
So why was Mr. Ji the one who rescued me?
Why did Mr. Ji get there before the police?
Or did the police rescue me first
and Mr. Ji showed up afterward...
I was kidnapped right
after Zhou Yang went abroad.
Did Zhou's parents already know I existed?
Or was Ji Mingxuan trying to secure his sister's
happiness by getting rid of me as an obstacle?
Then why did he say he liked me?
Ji Mingxuan puts profit above everything.
He schemed to break us up.
All for the marriage alliance
between the Zhou and Ji families.
That's not true.
He did it for his sister.
How can you still believe his bullshit?
He knew perfectly well I never loved An'an.
He forced us together.
He wasn't doing it for his sister at all.
Even if Mr. Ji did it on purpose...
wasn't everything you did your own choice?
Weren't you willing to go abroad
with Miss Ji and to get engaged to her?
You clearly didn't love her.
Why did you deceive her feelings like that?
I...
I had the Zhou family behind me.
I had no choice.
You had no choice?
You're wrong.
You did have a choice.
You chose the life you have now.
Even if Mr. Ji hadn't said anything,
you'd still be doing the same thing.
Getting married.
Having kids.
And keeping me as your secret lover.
Zhou Yang.
You're just like them.
You're selfish.
And you put profit above everything.
People who truly love each other...
can't be torn apart by any
scheme or underhanded tactic.
If they do,
it only means they didn't
love each other enough.
If...
I...
If I could give up everything...
Mo.
Could we...
Could we start over?
It's impossible.
Mo.
You're the only one I love.
I...
I can't live without you.
You're the only one in my heart.
Please.
Mo.
Let go.
Let go
I said it's impossible.
An'an.
An'an, let me explain.
It's not what it looks like.
There's no need to explain.
I heard everything.
Zhou Yang.
I couldn't believe what
your brother told me at first.
You...
What you just said was true...?
You never loved me...?
Yes.
I never loved you.
Bastard.
Then why did you lie to me?
Why did I lie to you?
Ask your wonderful big brother.
If he hadn't threatened and bribed me
and used every trick in the book,
how could I have been with you?
How could I have left Shen Mo?
Big Brother Shen.
You...
So you and my brother were fake too...
You two are the real couple.
Right?
An'an.
No.
I understand now.
Liars.
You're all liars.
It's not like that.
An'an, let me explain.
An'an.
Don't follow me.
Please.
Why did you say those things to An'an?
What else could I do?
Lie to her for the rest of her life/?
Mr. Ji.
An'an knows.
Knows what?
About Zhou Yang and me.
Where's An'an?
She ran out.
She left.
An'an.
Please let her be okay.
Shen Mo.
Where's An'an?
Where did she go?
Where are they?
Shen Mo.
Where did the girl who fainted go?
Did you see her?
I didn't see her.
Zhou Yang.
Come here.
Mom.
An'an...
You good-for-nothing disgrace.
You're here.
How is Miss Ji?
She's still in surgery.
What's her condition?
Have a seat.
An'an is eight years younger than me.
The year she was born,
it happened to be spring.
The breeze felt warm against my skin.
And carried the faint scent of flowers.
An'an was always easygoing as a child.
She never cried or threw tantrums.
She'd smile brightly at everyone she met.
She looked so much like my mother.
Sadly, not long after giving birth to her,
my mother passed away.
From congenital heart disease.
An'an inherited it too.
Medicine is so advanced now.
Heart disease isn't untreatable.
That's true.
She had surgery when she was very young.
Sadly, it didn't work very well.
No one knew when she might leave this world.
So I swore as a child
that I'd give An'an anything she wanted.
I wanted her to stay alive
every minute of every day.
And to live happily.
But the one thing she wanted was Zhou Yang.
I've never liked Zhou Yang.
But it didn't matter.
As long as An'an was happy.
Everyone welcomed the marriage
alliance between the Zhou and Ji families.
They just never expected...
...that I would become an obstacle.
Fortunately, Zhou Yang was smart.
He knew when to make compromises.
Since he was willing to cooperate,
I didn't mind giving An'an an illusion.
One that would make her happy.
As long as she was happy.
An'an.
How is An'an?
Get lost.
The patient is temporarily out of danger.
But her condition is still very unstable.
She can't endure any
more emotional distress.
Family members, please step aside.
Excuse me, please step aside.
An'an.
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
Big Brother.
An'an said she doesn't
want to see you.
Shen Mo, come here
I need to talk to you.
Shen Mo.
Mr. Ji.
Does Miss Ji also
not want to see me?
Shen Mo.
I should apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
Don't.
I was the one who told the Zhou family
about your relationship with Zhou Yang.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who did this to you.
I figured that out a long time ago.
But hearing all this from Mr. Ji himself...
This is for An'an.
To help her recover.
Yeah.
Mr. Ji.
Could you...
Shen Mo.
I did this to you.
And you still came.
You can't take all the blame
for what happened to me.
Our contract is over.
Go.
It's over.
Shen Mo.
Are you satisfied with
how things turned out?
I never thought things
would turn out this way
I don't want to lie to An'an anymore.
My heart still belongs to you.
You still have the nerve to say that.
You're completely beyond saving.
I've figured it out.
I can have nothing.
And I won't be tied down anymore.
Wasn't I helping you too?
You won't have to suffer at
Ji Mingxuan's side anymore.
Shen Mo.
To you, it was a shackle.
But to me, it never was.
Wait until I draw a Ferris wheel for you.
From when is this memory from?
Is this my memory?